Ice is a thriller, action, science fiction film directed by Nick Copus.
It is 2020.
Findings by environmental scientist Professor Thom Archer suggest that Halo, the corporate
energy company drilling on the Greenland Glacier are causing it to melt.
Archer's warnings are ignored, so he heads to the
Arctic to find indisputable evidence.
Upon arrival, he realizes humankind is under immediate
threat, and races home to save his family.
The glacier collapses, with devastating consequences.
Astonishing weather patterns emerge and plunge the
world's temperatures into steep decline.
Thom Archer, played by Richard Roxburgh.
Sarah, played by Frances O'Connor.
Jacqueline, played by Claire Forlani.
Stephen, played by Ben Cross.
Peterson, played by Stephen Moyer.
Milly, played by Brooke Williams.
Thin Ice (originally released as The Convincer) is a 2011 American black comedy film
directed by Jill Sprecher and starring Greg Kinnear, Alan Arkin and Billy Crudup.
The film explores themes of climate change, ice age,
polar bear, helicopter pilot, oil rig .
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.